Say, "Can't talk right now.
Hanging with my boyfriend.
(Leonard:)England sucks, you suck,
U.S.A. Number one."
Fine. "Hanging with my boyfriend.
Talk to you later."
(Penny:)- Happy?
- Yes. Thank you.
(Penny:)Mm-hm.
(Raj:)Huh.
- What did he say?
- Nothing.
(Leonard:)What?
"Did your boyfriend make you type that?"
(Leonard:)I hate this guy.
- Don't be like that.
- Oh, come on. Trust me, he's hitting on you.
(Penny:)He's not, we're just friends.
Is this gonna be a problem?
(Penny:)He's supposed to come over
tomorrow to work.
(Leonard:)Really? Here?
(Penny:)If it makes you uncomfortable, I'll switch
partners even though the thing's due...
(Penny:)...and everyone already has a partner
and I'll probably end up failing the class.